[SINGING]
She said, "You don't know me
You don't even care"
(Leonard:)Oh, yeah
(Sheldon:)Oh, good Lord.
She said, "You don't know me
You don't wear my chains"
(Leonard:)Oh, yeah
(Leonard(singing):)God, that's a good song.
(Sheldon:)If you're compiling a mix CD
for a double suicide.
(Sheldon:)Oh, I hope that scratching post
is for you.
(Leonard:)I know what you're thinking.
I've taken your asthma into account.
(Leonard:)There's a feline geneticist in San Diego...
...who's developed
the cutest little hypoallergenic calicos.
(Sheldon:)- Listen...
- I've been thinking about names.
(Leonard:)I'm kind of torn between Einstein,
Newton and Sergeant Fuzzy Boots.
Do you think you can satisfy
your need for a relationship...
(Sheldon:)...with a genetically altered cat?
(Leonard:)Maybe, if it's a cute little cuddly cat.